AKPALA BABA COSMOS

8, Alhaji Olawale Bakare Street, Bakare Estate, Agungi, Lagos State, Nigeria cosmosakpala@gmail.com +234 816 487 1848

OBJECTIVE

Dependable and quick thinking Creative Writer and Content Creator with a proven ability to write engaging and appealing content. Able to drive the increase in social media engagements and website traffic by at least 30%. Has an excellent command of grammar, strong editing skills and a long track record of researching and writing various topics.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Marketivy, Lagos

Social Media Manager (Freelance)

April 2019 - Present

- Developing articles and engaging a community of followers on social media platforms.
- Writes, edits posts, and promotes contents on the social media pages.
- Researching topics and verify factual information.

First City Monument Bank, Lagos

Social Media Manager (Freelance)

May 2019

- Created awareness on the company's new product.
- Engaged different marketing tools in order to promote product awareness.
- Developed contents for company's website and social media channels.

Eljon Fashion Limited

Social Media Manger (Freelance)

September 2018 - December 2018

- Followed trends for the social media pages
- Developed contents for social media pages.
- · Created graphic designs and rebranded company's logo.
- Generated leads and responded to enquiries.

Hello Naija Blog

Content Writing (Freelance)

March 2018 – July 2018

- Developed contents for company's website and media channels.
- Applied analytics tools to boost social media and website search
- · Wrote articles related to politics, entrepreneurship and lifestyle.
- Developed interesting contents which increased website traffic by 20%.

SKILLS AND EXPERTISE

- Content Creation
- Business Development
- Creative Writing Skills
- Social Media Management
- Procurement
- Operations
- People Management
- Microsoft (Word, Excel, PowerPoint)
- Research and Fact Finding
- Effective Communication

EDUCATION

Lagos State University, Ojo, Lagos - BA. English Language/Literary Studies

ACHIEVEMENTS

Anthology of 50 Young Nigerian Poets – The Sky Is Our Earth
Publisher – Write House Publishers
Date – September 2015

LANGUAGES

- English Fluent
- Yoruba Intermediate